ad-flow.com 2018-12-27

# PRIVACY POLICY | Suite 66

* * *

Suite 66 strongly believes in a consumer’s right to privacy. All web user data collected by Suite 66 as part of the ad serving process is not personally identifiable and is used in aggregate form.

This Privacy Policy covers the information we collect about you when you engage our services, or otherwise interact with us (for example, by attending our events). This policy also explains how we use information about you and how you can access and update certain information about you.

### COMPLIANCE WITH CASL, PIPEDA, GDPR

Our information and data management policies and practices comply with Canada’s Anti-Spam Legislation, the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act, and the EU’s General Data Protection Regulation.

### USE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION:

Suite 66 does not sell or purchase information that is personally identifiable. Suite 66 acts as a sales representative for companies (“Publishers”) that would like to sell advertising on their websites or other digital platforms (eg. Facebook, Instagram, Twitter) to our Advertisers and their Agencies. We do not control or store any personally identifiable data collected by the Publishers we represent. We also make reasonable efforts to ensure the Publishers comply with privacy regulations as they apply to each user based on where they live.

In the course of conducting business, we work with companies to provide us with information that can help us target consumers on behalf of Advertisers and Agencies that work with us. In our dealings with these companies, we only access that information once it has been anonymized and/or aggregated. We do not access or store any data from these companies that could be considered personally identifiable. We also make reasonable efforts to ensure that these companies have processes and policies in place with respect to any personally identifiable data they collect.

In our business dealings with Publishers, Advertisers or their Agencies we do store personally identifiable data. This can include information such as names, addresses, email addresses, and phone numbers. We do this for purposes such as generating advertising agreements, billing, and human resource purposes (eg. job applications). Personally identifiable data in these cases will be maintained as long as reasonably required for regular business practices under applicable laws.

From time to time, we collect personally identifiable data as part of our marketing activities. For example, we may collect such data during an event we host. With respect to our company website (http://www.suite66.com) any personally identifiable data we collect for marketing purposes is collected through means that require explicit consent (eg. online forms for people to get in touch with us). This data will be maintained as long as reasonably required for regular business practices under applicable laws.

### CONSUMER CHOICE – OPT OUT:

Third party tracking cookies may be used in the ad-serving process to provide relevant advertising via behavioural targeting on desktop and mobile web browsers. Some of the ads you receive on Web pages are customized based on predictions about your interests generated from your visits to different Websites in a browser and on other devices you may use. This type of ad customization is sometimes called “online behavioral” or “interest-based” advertising. The Digital Advertising Alliance Canada principles apply to the use of data collected across multiple websites and/or applications in order to predict user preferences and to show ads that are most likely to be of interest to users.

Consumers who are interested in opting out of being behaviorally targeted can set their “opt-out” preferences at the Digital Advertising Alliance Canada – [http://www.youradchoices.ca/choice](http://youradchoices.ca/choices). You may still receive other types of online advertising from participating companies, and these companies may still collect information for other purposes.

The “opt-out” cookie must remain on your computer in order for you to be recognized as an “opt-out” user. This means that if you use multiple computers or multiple browsers you will need to “opt-out” of receiving cookies on each computer and for each browser. Also, if you change computers or delete cookies from your computer you will need to repeat this “opt-out” process.

To “opt out” of receiving targeted advertising on mobile devices, please see up-to-date manufacturer information. At the time of this policy, Android devices include this under Settings > Google > Ads > Opt Out of Interest Based Ads; iOS devices include this under Settings > General > Privacy > Limit Ad Tracking.

### OPT-OUT OF SUITE 66 DATA COLLECTION

Additionally, you may click [here to “opt-out”](http://www.suite66.com/optout.html) of data collection and behaviourally targeted advertising from Suite 66. You will still continue to receive online advertisements from Suite 66 but these may not be relevant to you. Note that if you switch browsers, or to computers/devices where your browser settings are not automatically synchronized, you will need to complete the “opt-out” process each time. Finally, your browser settings must have cookies enabled and allow 3rd party cookies for the “opt-out” mechanism to work correctly.

### ACCESSIBLE CUSTOMER SERVICE FEEDBACK PROCESS

Customers and/or third parties who wish to provide feedback on the way Suite 66 provides services to people with disabilities can provide feedback in the following way(s): verbally, in person or by telephone in writing by letter or [email.](http://www.suite66.com/contact/)

### INQUIRIES / REQUESTS

You have the right to obtain our confirmation of whether we maintain personal information relating to you. Upon request, we will provide you with access to the personal information that we hold about you. You may also correct, amend, or delete the personal information we hold about you. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data, should direct his query to the contact information provided below. If requested to remove data, we will respond within a reasonable time frame.

In writing:

Attn: Data Officer

Suite 66  
366 Adelaide St W. Suite 600  
Toronto, Ontario  
M5V 1R9, Canada

By Phone: (416) 628-5565  
By Email: [dataofficer@suite66.com](mailto:dataofficer@suite66.com)

Last Updated: June 12, 2018
